{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133596164","data":{"timestamp":" 947133596164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_G-N-Y"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133600103","data":{"timestamp":" 947133600103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_E-Y-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133605810","data":{"timestamp":" 947133605809"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_E-Y-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133610082","data":{"timestamp":" 947133610082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_J-A-R"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133614531","data":{"timestamp":" 947133614531"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-B-Y"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133632395","data":{"timestamp":" 947133632395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_G-N-CH"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133637971","data":{"timestamp":" 947133637970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_G-N-CH"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133647179","data":{"timestamp":" 947133647179"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_M-I-CH"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133651997","data":{"timestamp":" 947133651997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_J-K-Y"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133662810","data":{"timestamp":" 947133662810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_O-G-S"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133669261","data":{"timestamp":" 947133669261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_O-G-S"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133673314","data":{"timestamp":" 947133673314"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-O-T"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133678694","data":{"timestamp":" 947133678694"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_E-T-Y"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133684263","data":{"timestamp":" 947133684263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-Z-A"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133690981","data":{"timestamp":" 947133690981"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_P-F-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133699221","data":{"timestamp":" 947133699221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_P-F-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133710214","data":{"timestamp":" 947133710214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_J-A-CH"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133715877","data":{"timestamp":" 947133715876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-K-F"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133720202","data":{"timestamp":" 947133720202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_M-CH-L"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133726853","data":{"timestamp":" 947133726853"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-D-Z"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133731120","data":{"timestamp":" 947133731119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_B-R-T"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133735309","data":{"timestamp":" 947133735309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_S-D-W"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133740752","data":{"timestamp":" 947133740752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-T-K"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133747454","data":{"timestamp":" 947133747454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_B-A-L"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133755152","data":{"timestamp":" 947133755152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_B-A-L"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133762792","data":{"timestamp":" 947133762792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_B-A-L"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133774536","data":{"timestamp":" 947133774536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_I-W-O"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133780898","data":{"timestamp":" 947133780897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_I-W-O"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133794858","data":{"timestamp":" 947133794858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_N-D-I"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133800309","data":{"timestamp":" 947133800309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_N-D-I"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133804074","data":{"timestamp":" 947133804074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_F-U-S"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133808513","data":{"timestamp":" 947133808513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_S-P-M"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947133814281","data":{"timestamp":" 947133814281"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_073939"," gameId":" e77ffb33-f5ec-4d8d-ad3c-cd1cce99bdb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_M_S-P-M"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}